Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and other media, 1880 -- 2000; 1915 -- 1999; MS024.007; 34.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 58 Audiovisual Object(s); 727 Digital Object(s)
  - Photo negatives, 1916 -- 1978; MS024.007.147
    - Three Mile Island, MS024.007.147.00057 (Box 147)
    - Grand Canyon, 1918; MS024.007.147.00058 (Box 147)
    - Colorado, 1919; MS024.007.147.00059 (Box 147)
    - Camp Bourget, MS024.007.147.00060 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00061 (Box 147)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.147.00062 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00063 (Box 147)
    - Fete Day, 1938; MS024.007.147.00064 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00065 (Box 147)
    - Airplane pictures, Carlstram Field, MS024.007.147.00066 (Box 147)
    - Spanish trip with Lottie and others, 1933; MS024.007.147.00067 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00068 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00069 (Box 147)
    - Loose negatives/no envelope, MS024.007.147.00070 (Box 147)
    - Spain, MS024.007.147.00071 (Box 147)
    - Autobus trips, MS024.007.147.00072 (Box 147)
    - Essex and groups, MS024.007.147.00073 (Box 147)
    - Donald R. MacJannet, MS024.007.147.00074 (Box 147)
    - Battlefields, MS024.007.147.00075 (Box 147)
    - Elms activities, MS024.007.147.00076 (Box 147)
    - Country scenes, rout to camp, MS024.007.147.00077 (Box 147)
    - Battlefields, MS024.007.147.00078 (Box 147)
    - Commencement, 1927; MS024.007.147.00079 (Box 147)
      Commencement; MacJannet School
    - Spring trip to the Pyrenees, MS024.007.147.00080 (Box 147)
    - Jean, MS024.007.147.00081 (Box 147)
      Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - Chamonix, MS024.007.147.00082 (Box 147)
    - Camp track meet, MS024.007.147.00083 (Box 147)
    - Camp fete, 1929; MS024.007.147.00084 (Box 147)
    - Mont Saint Michel trip, MS024.007.147.00085 (Box 147)
    - Camp hikes, MS024.007.147.00086 (Box 147)
    - Camp dramatics, MS024.007.147.00087 (Box 147)
    - Track at the Elms School, MS024.007.147.00088 (Box 147)
    - Bourget hikes, MS024.007.147.00089 (Box 147)
    - Camp acrobatics, MS024.007.147.00090 (Box 147)
    - Elms excursions, MS024.007.147.00091 (Box 147)
    - Diving, MS024.007.147.00092 (Box 147)
    - Chamonix Ice Cavern, MS024.007.147.00093 (Box 147)
    - Camp friends, MS024.007.147.00094 (Box 147)
    - Pagent - Golden Fleece, MS024.007.147.00095 (Box 147)
    - Regatta - Annecy, MS024.007.147.00096 (Box 147)
    - Marian Faithful, MS024.007.147.00097 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00098 (Box 147)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.147.00099 (Box 147)
    - Chamonix, MS024.007.148.00001 (Box 148)
    - Masters, 1916 -- 1917; MS024.007.148.00002 (Box 148)
    - Camp Bourget, MS024.007.148.00003 (Box 148)
    - Winter sports, Font Romeu, MS024.007.148.00004 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00005 (Box 148)
    - Algerie Biskra, MS024.007.148.00006 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00007 (Box 148)
    - School dramatics, MS024.007.148.00008 (Box 148)
    - Camp, MS024.007.148.00009 (Box 148)
    - Annency camp films, 1925; MS024.007.148.00010 (Box 148)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.148.00011 (Box 148)
    - "Jean a gauche", MS024.007.148.00012 (Box 148)
    - Mostly camp, especially good films, MS024.007.148.00013 (Box 148)
    - Enlarge for best effect, MS024.007.148.00014 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00015 (Box 148)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.148.00016 (Box 148)
    - Lottie and Jean, MS024.007.148.00017 (Box 148)
      MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00018 (Box 148)
    - Winter sports, MS024.007.148.00019 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00020 (Box 148)
    - Yellowstone, 1919; MS024.007.148.00021 (Box 148)
    - Snow House, MS024.007.148.00022 (Box 148)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.148.00023 (Box 148)
    - Winter sports, MS024.007.148.00024 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00025 (Box 148)
    - Winter sports, MS024.007.148.00026 (Box 148)
    - New York, 1940; MS024.007.148.00027 (Box 148)
    - Trip to Italy, Woodie - Sutherlands, MS024.007.148.00028 (Box 148)
      Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"
    - Camp: lodge from the water, MS024.007.148.00029 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00030 (Box 148)
    - Camp Veysier, MS024.007.148.00031 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00032 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00033 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00034 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00035 (Box 148)
    - Staff at Camp Verysien, MS024.007.148.00036 (Box 148)
    - School, MS024.007.148.00037 (Box 148)
    - Travel camps, summer, 1940; MS024.007.148.00038 (Box 148)
    - War winter at Talloires, 1939 -- 1940; MS024.007.148.00039 (Box 148)
    - Miscellaneous films, MS024.007.148.00040 (Box 148)
      Negatives: sailboat with 2 masts, upper camp cook-out, camp tent from interior, 2 boys+castle+sake, dragon, dining, softie+j+fishing, Valero in shop, Peter Tompkins, Birand, Mrs Stewart's car
    - Jardin des Plantes, Paris, MS024.007.148.00041 (Box 148)
    - Elms Prieure (Winter), MS024.007.148.00042 (Box 148)
    - In army uniform, MS024.007.148.00043 (Box 148)
    - Mt. Washington, Madison Huts, MS024.007.148.00044 (Box 148)
    - Miscellaneous films, MS024.007.148.00045 (Box 148)
      Negatives: camp+trips+prewar, choice for art studies
    - Family, MS024.007.148.00046 (Box 148)
    - Helga, MS024.007.148.00047 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00048 (Box 148)
    - Lottie, MS024.007.148.00049 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00050 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00051 (Box 148)
    - Camp films, MS024.007.148.00052 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00053 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00054 (Box 148)
    - Seen, MS024.007.148.00055 (Box 148)
    - Christmas, 1939; MS024.007.148.00056 (Box 148)
    - Hayes, MS024.007.148.00057 (Box 148)
    - Camp grounds, MS024.007.148.00058 (Box 148)
    - Films of camp, MS024.007.148.00059 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00060 (Box 148)
    - View of camp (copies), MS024.007.148.00061 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00062 (Box 148)
    - Rose Fuller, MS024.007.148.00063 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00064 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00065 (Box 148)
    - Congamond, MS024.007.148.00066 (Box 148)
    - Views of camp, MS024.007.148.00067 (Box 148)
    - Personal, MS024.007.148.00068 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00069 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00070 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00071 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00072 (Box 148)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.148.00073 (Box 148)
    - Posture pictures, MS024.007.148.00074 (Box 148)
    - Camp pictures (refugee children?), MS024.007.148.00075 (Box 148)
    - Chanoux, 1924 -- 1925; MS024.007.148.00076 (Box 148)
    - House Umsburg, MS024.007.149.00001 (Box 149)
    - Blensdorf, Sweden, MS024.007.149.00002 (Box 149)
    - Blensdorf, Sweden, MS024.007.149.00003 (Box 149)
    - The Koos, the Helburns, the Ashbys, and the Muketji family, MS024.007.149.00004 (Box 149)
    - Photos of Richmond Holder, MS024.007.149.00005 (Box 149)
    - Group Elms, Prince Philip, MS024.007.149.00006 (Box 149)
      Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh; MacJannet School
    - Camp, MS024.007.149.00007 (Box 149)
    - MacJannet family, MS024.007.149.00008 (Box 149)
    - Excursions in France, MS024.007.149.00009 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00010 (Box 149)
    - Peter Pan, MS024.007.149.00011 (Box 149)
    - Junior school, MS024.007.149.00012 (Box 149)
    - Army, MS024.007.149.00013 (Box 149)
    - Camp, 1946; MS024.007.149.00014 (Box 149)
    - School and camp, MS024.007.149.00015 (Box 149)
    - Camp, 1946; MS024.007.149.00016 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00017 (Box 149)
    - Sam Stokes, MS024.007.149.00018 (Box 149)
    - Tufts College, MS024.007.149.00019 (Box 149)
      Tufts College
    - Good camp before war, MS024.007.149.00020 (Box 149)
    - Camp, 1946; MS024.007.149.00021 (Box 149)
    - Trip to Norway, MS024.007.149.00022 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00023 (Box 149)
    - Excursions from St. Cloud, MS024.007.149.00024 (Box 149)
    - Parades camp, MS024.007.149.00025 (Box 149)
    - St. Albans, MS024.007.149.00026 (Box 149)
    - Personalities at camp and my portraits, MS024.007.149.00027 (Box 149)
    - St. Cloud films, MS024.007.149.00028 (Box 149)
    - Camp water sports, MS024.007.149.00029 (Box 149)
    - Camp, 1947; MS024.007.149.00030 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00031 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00032 (Box 149)
    - Mountain climbing, MS024.007.149.00033 (Box 149)
    - Maj. Fred B. Asche, Camp Sibert, and Gadsden, Alabama, MS024.007.149.00034 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00035 (Box 149)
    - Alwarda Casselman, MS024.007.149.00036 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00037 (Box 149)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.149.00038 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00039 (Box 149)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.149.00040 (Box 149)
    - Fort Monroe, 1918; MS024.007.149.00041 (Box 149)
    - Field Day, 1918; MS024.007.149.00042 (Box 149)
    - Girls school and garden party, 1918; MS024.007.149.00043 (Box 149)
    - Tufts College, 1918; MS024.007.149.00044 (Box 149)
    - Sower School, 1916 -- 1917; MS024.007.149.00045 (Box 149)
    - Trip west, 1920; MS024.007.149.00046 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00047 (Box 149)
    - Flag raising, MS024.007.149.00048 (Box 149)
    - Dot and Marj Hart, MS024.007.149.00049 (Box 149)
    - Elms School, MS024.007.149.00050 (Box 149)
    - Iola Blodgett, MS024.007.149.00051 (Box 149)
    - Irene Randall, 1917; MS024.007.149.00052 (Box 149)
    - St. James baseball trials, 1918; MS024.007.149.00053 (Box 149)
    - Park Field, 1919; MS024.007.149.00054 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00055 (Box 149)
    - Sun Valley, MS024.007.149.00056 (Box 149)
    - Trocadiro School, MS024.007.149.00057 (Box 149)
    - Veysier Camp, MS024.007.149.00058 (Box 149)
    - Trip to Algeria, MS024.007.149.00059 (Box 149)
    - School, MS024.007.149.00060 (Box 149)
    - Views of camp, MS024.007.149.00061 (Box 149)
    - Upper camp, MS024.007.149.00062 (Box 149)
    - Camp, 1939; MS024.007.149.00063 (Box 149)
    - Camp, MS024.007.149.00064 (Box 149)
    - Orphans with labels, MS024.007.149.00065 (Box 149)
    - Unlabeled, MS024.007.149.00066 (Box 149)
    - Jean in Germany, MS024.007.149.00067 (Box 149)
    - African trip, MS024.007.150.00001 (Box 150)
    - Groups in Africa, MS024.007.150.00002 (Box 150)
    - Italian trip, MS024.007.150.00003 (Box 150)
    - Norwegian trip, MS024.007.150.00004 (Box 150)
    - Mr. MacJannet, MS024.007.150.00005 (Box 150)
    - Entire group at camp, MS024.007.150.00006 (Box 150)
    - School groups at the Elms, MS024.007.150.00007 (Box 150)
    - Pierre Fond, MS024.007.150.00008 (Box 150)
    - On boat during USA trip, MS024.007.150.00009 (Box 150)
    - Rouen trip, Jean and Donald MacJannet, MS024.007.150.00010 (Box 150)
      Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Costume fete at Annecy, MS024.007.150.00011 (Box 150)
    - Camp group, MS024.007.150.00012 (Box 150)
    - Annecy annals, MS024.007.150.00013 (Box 150)
    - Annecy annals, MS024.007.150.00014 (Box 150)
    - School trips, 1935; MS024.007.150.00015 (Box 150)
    - MacJannet negatives, loose, 1930; MS024.007.150.00016 (Box 150)
    - Tufts College reunion negatives taken by MacJannet, 1948; MS024.007.150.00017 (Box 150)
    - Anita and 'Woody' Woodworth, 1928; MS024.007.150.00018 (Box 150)
    - MacJannet camp negatives, 1930; MS024.007.150.00019 (Box 150)
    - The official opening of the Tufts European Center, 1978; MS024.007.151.00001 (Box 151)
      Tufts University; European Center
    - Inauguration, 1978; MS024.007.151.00002 (Box 151)
  - Emory Foster's camp scrapbook, 1909 -- 1914; MS024.007.159 (Box 159)
  - MacJannet European vacation, correspondence, scrapbook, 1929 -- 1936; MS024.007.160 (Box 160)
  - Emory Foster's drama Scrapbook, 1917 -- 1923; MS024.007.161 (Box 161)
  - Video tape, MS024.007.169 (Box data_value_missing_3a078d69d13d17d13a86f0f05ae9ae82)
  - Magnetic audio tape, 7ft 5 in., Halbspur beide spuren bespielt, MS024.007.170 (Box data_value_missing_3a078d69d13d17d13a86f0f05ae9ae82)
  - Folk Dances, 1937; MS024.007.171.00001 (Box 171)
  - Unidentified loose film, MS024.007.171.00002 (Box 171)
  - Lignac, MS024.007.171.00003 (Box 171)
  - Unidentified film, MS024.007.171.00004 (Box 171)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.178 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film Gerda/ Upper camp picnic, Spain, MS024.007.179 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Folk dance - The Elms, MS024.007.180 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Views - Talloires, MS024.007.181 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.182 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of film color of trips, MS024.007.183 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Old Prof. Monkey, MS024.007.184 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.185 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.186 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.187 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.188 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.189 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.190 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of film color of trips, MS024.007.191 (Box data_value_missing_5d1f20a9ae06b7449425198efe2b76ff)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of film color of trips, MS024.007.192 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of film color, Spain, 1933; MS024.007.193 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.194 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of color of trips, MS024.007.195 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.196 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film, untitled, MS024.007.197 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film: Camp 1957 - Reel II Excursions, climb Sigermain, MS024.007.198 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film: Bits of film color of trips, MS024.007.199 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet film: Spain, 1955; MS024.007.200 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - Magnetic audio tape - 'Conie', MS024.007.201 (Box data_value_missing_9ab9ba8fbc62179cbfd32ce677ae548d)
  - MacJannet Film of Sun valley 1941 (Nr. 21), Sun valley 1942 (Nr. 11), Camp 1937 (nr. 35), 1937 -- 1942; MS024.007.207 (Box 207)
  - MacJannet film, Spain, color, MS024.007.208 (Box 208)
  - MacJannet film, Sun Valley summer color, 1940; MS024.007.209 (Box 209)
  - MacJannet film, Phillip: When daddy was a boy, MS024.007.210 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
  - MacJannet betamax, Mr. Merieux, Inauguration du centre de pa Tufts University, 1979; MS024.007.211 (Box 211)
  - Film and Video reels, MS024.007.216 (Box 216)
  - Scrapbook of Emory Foster, 1920; MS024.007.221 (Box 221)
  - Emory Foster scrapbook, 1914; MS024.007.222.00001 (Box 222)
  - Scrapbook of Emory Foster, 1929 -- 1935; MS024.007.222.00002 (Box 222)
  - MacJannet slides of Japan, MS024.007.223.00001 (Box 223)
  - MacJannet slides of Ikebana and foliage, MS024.007.223.00002 (Box 223)
  - MacJannet negatives, MS024.007.225 (Box 225)
  - MacJannet photos from other series, 1920 -- 1995; MS024.007.226 (Box 226)
  - MacJannet glass plate negatives, MS024.007.227 (Box 227)
  - MacJannet photos from other series, 1920 -- 1995; MS024.007.228 (Box 228)
  - MacJannet photos from other series, 1920 -- 1995; MS024.007.229 (Box 229)
  - MacJannet photos from other series, 1920 -- 1995; MS024.007.230 (Box 230)
  - Emory and Jean Foster, photos, 1925 -- 1930; MS024.007.231.00001 (Box 231)
  - Emory Foster's photos, 1925; MS024.007.231.00002 (Box 231)
  - Emory Foster's photos, 1925; MS024.007.231.00003 (Box 231)
  - Photos collected by Jean MacJannet Foster, 1930 -- 1950; MS024.007.231.00004 (Box 231)
  - Emory Foster, photos, 1930; MS024.007.231.00005 (Box 231)
  - MacJannet Camp and School photos, 1930; MS024.007.231.00006 (Box 231)
  - Folders of Blensdorf family photos, 1925 -- 1935; MS024.007.231.00007 (Box 231)
  - MacJannet block plates, 1930; MS024.007.232 (Box 232)
  - VHS and Digital video of MacJannet film from Rocky Carzo, 1995; MS024.007.236 (Box 236)
    Former barcode 39090011479017g.
  - Audio cassettes from Rocky Carzo, 1975 -- 2000; MS024.007.238
    - Mrs. MacJannet Memorial Celebration at Talloires, 2000-06-10; MS024.007.238.00001 (Box 238)
      Used for her memorial film, "La vie en rose."
    - MacJannet ceremony, Talloires, 2000-06-10; MS024.007.238.00002 (Box 238)
      Rocky Carzo used for film.
    - MacJannet ceremony, Talloires, 2000-06-10; MS024.007.238.00003 (Box 238)
      Rocky Carzo used for film "La vie en rose."
    - Cassette recorded at the memorial celebartion of Mrs. MacJannet in Talloires, 2000-06-10; MS024.007.238.00004 (Box 238)
    - MacJannet film audio tape with Rob Hollister and Andrew McClellan, 2000-05-11; MS024.007.239.00001 (Box 239)
    - Mr. MacJannet and Professor Simches on MacJannet Camp history 1940-51, recorded, 1975; MS024.007.239.00002 (Box 239)
    - Mrs. MacJannet, 1990; MS024.007.239.00003 (Box 239)
    - Mrs. MacJannet, audio for "France Rebuilds", 1993-06-29; MS024.007.239.00004 (Box 239)
  - MacJannet film of Tufts University, 1949 -- 1950; MS024.007.242 (Box 242)
  - Films of camp, 1946 -- 1957; MS024.007.243 (Box 243)
  - MacJannet film, The MacJannet Legacy-- Tufts European Center Talloires, France, MS024.007.244 (Box 244)
  - MacJannet film, La Vie en Rose: Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet 1901-1999, MS024.007.245 (Box 245)
  - MacJannet Camp reunion at the campsite in Angon, 1998-06; MS024.007.DO.00887; Unknown (Box Shared 140)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; photographic print; Snyder, Willard; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet Camp
  - Students from the MacJannet School in Paris, 1932; MS024.007.DO.01452; Unknown (Box Shared 61)
    Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet campers and counselors, 1935; MS024.007.DO.01453; Unknown (Box Shared 61)
  - Campers perform, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01454; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    MacJannet scrapbook 18, p. 9, # 18
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, 1980; MS024.007.DO.01455; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    MacJannet scrapbook 17, p. 11, #34
  - MacJannet Schools field trip, 1925; MS024.007.DO.01456; Unknown (Box 11)
    MacJannet scrapbook 17, p. 5, #9
    Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Students make music in a MacJannet School room, 1925; MS024.007.DO.01457; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    MacJannet scrapbook 18, p. 20 #37
    Students; Music and musical performances; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet in front of the Priory, Talloires, 1975; MS024.007.DO.01458; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    MacJannet scrapbook 17, p. 12, #40
    People; Buildings; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Tufts for aye, 1978-09-24; MS024.007.DO.01459; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Taken by Marsten Balch, MacJannet scrapbook 17, p. 5 # 17.
  - MacJannet Schools bus field trip, 1928; MS024.007.DO.01460; Unknown (Box 11)
    MacJannet scrapbook 18, p. 18, #34
  - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet in the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.DO.01461; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    MacJannet scrapbook 17, p. 12 #39
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1998; MS024.007.DO.01462; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
  - Dance performance by campers, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01463; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    MacJannet scrapbook 28, #12
    People; Children; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Swimming at camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01464; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    MacJannet scrapbook 28, # 14
    Children; Swimming; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Diving at camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01465; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    MacJannet scrapbook 23, leaf 11
    Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Dancing at camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01466; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    Children; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Fastest boat on the lake is putting on a show, 1961; MS024.007.DO.01467; Unknown (Box 78)
    MacJannet scrapbook (1961) p. 14
    People; Children; Boats and boating; Lakes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - View of MacJannet camp from the mountain, 1961; MS024.007.DO.01468; Unknown (Box 78)
    MacJannet scrapbook (1961), p. 5
    People; Views; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Elms students in front of the Eiffel Tower, 1928; MS024.007.DO.01469; Unknown (Box Shared 61)
    Students; People; Children; Faculty; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Amelia Earhart, aviatrice, speaks to students at the MacJannet school, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01471; Unknown (Box 7)
    People; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Earhart, Amelia; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Wedding photo of Jean MacJannet and Emory Foster, 1929-09-29; MS024.007.DO.01472; Unknown (Box 24)
    scrapbook23, leaf 28
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; Foster, Emory
  - MacJannet School (Elms) team, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01473; Unknown (Box 19)
    scrapbook 26
    Students; Athletics; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Elms School sports team, 1930; MS024.007.DO.01474; Unknown (Box 19)
    Students; Athletics; People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Students in front of Elms school building, 1928; MS024.007.DO.01475; Unknown (Box 3)
    Students; Buildings; Children; Faculty; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Dining room at the Elms school, 1925; MS024.007.DO.01476; Unknown (Box 7)
    scrapbook 29
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Bedroom at the Elms school, 1925; MS024.007.DO.01477; Unknown (Box 7)
  - Bathroom at the Elms school, 1925; MS024.007.DO.01478; Unknown (Box 7)
  - Salute at MacJannet camp, 1935; MS024.007.DO.01479; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_77f9b4c07bcd448a5395419f5b81a72f)
    scrapbook 22, leaf 16